Guide to the Norman Dorsen Papers TAM.251
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Writings, speeches, and public appearances.
  - Writings - The Unpredictable Constitution, 1989-2006 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    Includes one letter from U.S. Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg, one letter from U.S. Supreme Court Justice William J. Brennan, and two letters from U.S. Supreme Court Justice John Paul Stevens.
  - Writings - Village Voice, 1961-1962 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Writings - Village Voice, 1963-1965 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Writings - Village Voice, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Writings - Village Voice, 1973-1986 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Writings - Women's Name - articles, etc., 1975-1985 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Series IV: Subject files.
  - Abe Beame Task Force on Human Rights, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - American Bar Association - Norman Dorsen as judge for Ross Essay on "The Right to Dissent in a Free Society", 1969 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Bakke, 1976-1978 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Bakke, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Bakke (Post-Bakke), 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Battery Park City Authority Liberty Walk Committee (consultancy), 1986-1988 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Biographical information about Norman Dorsen, 1971-1984 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Biographical information about Norman Dorsen, 1985-1987 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Biographical information about Norman Dorsen - Harvard Civil Rights - Civil Liberties Law Review 27(2) (Summer 1992), special issue dedicated to Norman Dorsen. (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Biographical information about Norman Dorsen - Including publications information, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Biographical information about Norman Dorsen - Including publications information, 1983-2007 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Biographical information about Norman Dorsen - New York University Annual Survey of American Law 58(1) (2001), special issue dedicated to Norman Dorsen. (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Black-Jewish Relations - 92nd Street "Y", 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Carter Administration, 1977-1979 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Center for International Policy - Cuba mission, 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Channel 13 - TV pilot program "New Roads to Justice" (consultancy), 1970-1976 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Citizens' Board of Inquiry into Hunger and Malnutrition in the U.S. - Hunger in the U.S., 1967-1972 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Citizens' Board of Inquiry into Hunger and Malnutrition in the U.S. - Reports and statements, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Citizens' Inquiry on Parole and Criminal Justice, 1972-1975 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Citizens' Inquiry on Parole and Criminal Justice, 1972-1975 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Civil liberties, miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Civil liberties, miscellaneous, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Civil liberties, miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Civil liberties, miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Civil liberties, miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Civil liberties, miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Civil liberties, miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Civil liberties, miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Civil liberties, miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Civil liberties, miscellaneous, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Civil liberties, miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Committee for Public Justice - ACLU Foundation, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Committee for Public Justice - Bicentennial, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Committee for Public Justice - Convocation, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Committee for Public Justice - Early activities, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Committee for Public Justice - Executive meeting, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Committee for Public Justice - FBI conference, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Committee for Public Justice - FBI Post-conference, 1973-1975 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Committee for Public Justice - FBI Post-conference, 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Committee for Public Justice - FBI Post-conference, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Committee for Public Justice - Finances, 1972-1978 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Committee for Public Justice - Founding, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Committee for Public Justice - General, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Committee for Public Justice - General, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Committee for Public Justice - General, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Committee for Public Justice - General, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Committee for Public Justice - General, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Committee for Public Justice - General, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Committee for Public Justice - General, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Committee for Public Justice - General, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Committee for Public Justice - Government secrecy conference, 1972-1974 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Committee for Public Justice - Grand Jury conference, 1972-1974 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Committee for Public Justice - Justice Department conference, Undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Committee for Public Justice - Justice Department watch, 1977-1981 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Committee for Public Justice - Membership, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Committee for Public Justice - Personnel, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Committee for Public Justice - Projects, 1971-1973 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Community Action for Legal Services, 1967-1969 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Cranston, Alan, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Emergency Civil Liberties Committee, 1961-1971 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Horizon Communications (Board of Directors membership)., 1985-1987 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - House Un-American Activities Committee, 1961-1966 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - House Un-American Activities Committee, 1967-1971 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Judicial Selection - Democratic County Committee, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Kennedy, Robert F., 1965 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    Includes three letters from U.S. Senator Robert F. Kennedy.
  - Kennedy, Robert F., 1966 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    Includes four letters from U.S. Senator Robert F. Kennedy.
  - Kennedy, Robert F., 1967-1971 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Kennedy, Robert F. - Birth Control, 1963-1982 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    Includes one letter from U.S. Senator Robert F. Kennedy.
  - Koch, Ed, 1966-1968 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Koch, Ed, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Koch, Ed, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Koch, Ed, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Koch, Ed, 1975-1976 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Koch, Ed - Book review correspondence re: Koch, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Koch, Ed - Selective Conscientious Objection, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Lawyers Committee for Human Rights (LCHR) - Activities of the New York office, Apr 1995 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - LCHR - Administration, 1995-1999 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - LCHR - Archives, 1996-1998 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - LCHR - Asylum, 1995-2000 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - LCHR - Board of Directors, 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - LCHR - Board of Directors, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - LCHR - Board of Directors, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - LCHR - Board of Directors, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - LCHR - Board of Directors, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - LCHR - Board of Directors, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - LCHR - Business and human rights, Aug 1996 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - LCHR - Chairman, 1995-2000 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - LCHR - Committees, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - LCHR - Economic and social rights, 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - LCHR - Egypt and the Middle East, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - LCHR - Egypt and the Middle East, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - LCHR - Egypt and the Middle East, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - LCHR - Egypt and the Middle East, 1997-1999 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - LCHR - Executive Director search, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - LCHR - Expenses, 1996-1999 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - LCHR - Freedom of Association, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - LCHR - Fundraising and development, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - LCHR - Fundraising and development, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - LCHR - Fundraising and development, 1999-2000 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - LCHR - General, 1984-1987 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - LCHR - General, 1984-1987 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - LCHR - General, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - LCHR - General, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - LCHR - General, 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - LCHR - General, 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - LCHR - Harvard Law School Conference on Business and Human Rights, 1996-1999 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - LCHR - Henry J. Steiner Book Party fundraiser, 1995-1996 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - LCHR - Human rights theory, Feb 1997 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - LCHR - International Criminal Court, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - LCHR - International Criminal Court, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - LCHR - International Criminal Court, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    Includes one letter from U.S. President Bill Clinton.
  - LCHR - International Criminal Court, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - LCHR - Law firm appeal, 1995-1999 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - LCHR - Lawyer-to-Lawyer Network, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - LCHR - Michael Posner correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - LCHR - Miscellaneous, 1995-1998 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - LCHR - National Council, 1995-1996 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - LCHR - National Council, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - LCHR - National Council, 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - LCHR - National Council, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - LCHR - National Outreach, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - LCHR - National Outreach, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - LCHR - National Outreach, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - LCHR - National Outreach, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - LCHR - National Outreach, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - LCHR - Nominating Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - LCHR - Nominating Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - LCHR - Nominating Committee, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - LCHR - Norman Dorsen election and reception, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - LCHR - Northern Ireland, 1995-1996 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - LCHR - Northern Ireland, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - LCHR - Northern Ireland, 1998-2001 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - LCHR - Organizational structure, 1992-1995 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - LCHR - Other organizations, 1995-1997 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - LCHR - Personnel, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - LCHR - Philippines mission, Jul 1988 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - LCHR - Philippines mission, Jul 1988 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - LCHR - Philippines mission, Jul 1988 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - LCHR - Planning Task Force, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - LCHR - Program and policy, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - LCHR - Program and policy, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - LCHR - Program and policy, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - LCHR - Program and policy, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - LCHR - Protection Program, 1998-1999 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - LCHR - Rule of Law Resolution, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - LCHR - Salaries, 1995-1999 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - LCHR - Strategic Planning Committee, 1998-2000 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - LCHR - United Nations, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - LCHR - United Nations Conference on International Criminal Court, Rome, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - LCHR - United States compliance, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - LCHR - Washington Office Advisory Council, 1995-1999 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - LCHR - Witness program, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - LCHR - Witness program, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - LCHR - Witness program, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - LCHR - Witness program, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - LCHR - Witness program, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - LCHR - World Bank, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Model Anti-Discrimination Act - Colorado Conference, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Model Anti-Discrimination Act - Comments on Chapter 7, 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Model Anti-Discrimination Act - Comments on Second Draft, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Model Anti-Discrimination Act - Commissions, Undated (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Model Anti-Discrimination Act - Discrimination - Sex, 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Model Anti-Discrimination Act - Drafts, Undated (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Model Anti-Discrimination Act - Drafts, Undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Model Anti-Discrimination Act - Education, 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Model Anti-Discrimination Act - Florida Meeting, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Model Anti-Discrimination Act - Fourth Draft, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Model Anti-Discrimination Act - Fourth Tentative Draft, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Model Anti-Discrimination Act - Harvard Law Review Article, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Model Anti-Discrimination Act - Hospitals, Undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Model Anti-Discrimination Act - Housing, Undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Model Anti-Discrimination Act - Kentucky Civil Rights Act, 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Model Anti-Discrimination Act - Legislatures, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Model Anti-Discrimination Act - Miscellaneous, 1957-1963 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Model Anti-Discrimination Act - Miscellaneous, 1963-1965 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Model Anti-Discrimination Act - Miscellaneous, 1961-1968 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Model Anti-Discrimination Act - Model Civil Rights Acts, Undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Model Anti-Discrimination Act - Montreal Meeting, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Model Anti-Discrimination Act - New York Law Revision, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Model Anti-Discrimination Act - Press, 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Model Anti-Discrimination Act - Press, 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Model Anti-Discrimination Act - Second Draft, 1963-1965 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Model Anti-Discrimination Act - States, 1967-1972 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Model Anti-Discrimination Act - Third Draft, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Model Anti-Discrimination Act - Third Tentative Draft, 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Model Anti-Discrimination Act - Third Tentative Draft (Comments), 1966 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - National Coalition Against Censorship, 1978-1987 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - New York City Bar Association - Ethics Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - New York City Bar Association - Special Committee on Courtroom Conduct - Briefs and judicial opinions, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - New York City Bar Association - Special Committee on Courtroom Conduct - Consultants - Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - New York City Bar Association - Special Committee on Courtroom Conduct - Magazine and law review articles, 1970-1974 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - New York City Bar Association - Special Committee on Courtroom Conduct - Material distributed to the committee: rules, judicial conferences, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - New York City Bar Association - Special Committee on Courtroom Conduct - Meetings, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - New York City Bar Association - Special Committee on Courtroom Conduct - Memoranda - Consultants, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - New York City Bar Association - Special Committee on Courtroom Conduct - Memoranda - Leon Friedman, 1970-1974 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - New York City Bar Association - Special Committee on Courtroom Conduct - Minutes - Committee meetings, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - New York City Bar Association - Special Committee on Courtroom Conduct - Newspaper clippings, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - New York City Bar Association - Special Committee on Courtroom Conduct - Official correspondence, 1967-1974 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - New York City Bar Association - Special Committee on Courtroom Conduct - Questionnaire and interviews, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - New York City Bar Association - Special Committee on Courtroom Conduct - Taylor Amendment, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - New York City Commission on the Status of Women, 1979-1981 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - New York City Court of Appeals - Judge L. Cook., 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 1981 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - New York Civil Liberties Union, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - New York Civil Liberties Union - Hentoff Controversy, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - New York State Bar Association - Committee on Legal Education and Admission to the Bar, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - New York State Bar Association - Committee on Legal Education and Admission to the Bar, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - New York State Bar Association - Committee on Legal Education and Admission to the Bar, 1975-1976 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - North American Religious Liberties Association, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Office of the Secretary of the Army (OSA) - Correspondence, Jul 1953 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - OSA - Army Brief Committee Report (Army-McCarthy Hearings), Undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - OSA - Biographical Sketches, Undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - OSA - Correspondence, Aug 1953 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - OSA - Correspondence, Sep 1953 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - OSA - Correspondence, Oct 1953 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - OSA - Correspondence, Nov 1953 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - OSA - Correspondence, Dec 1953 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - OSA - Correspondence, Jan 1954 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - OSA - Correspondence, Feb 1954 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - OSA - Correspondence, Mar 1954 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - OSA - Correspondence, Apr 1954 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - OSA - Correspondence, Jun 1954 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - OSA - Correspondence, Jul 1954 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - OSA - Correspondence, Aug 1954 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - OSA - Correspondence, Sep 1954 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - OSA - Correspondence, Oct 1954 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - OSA - Correspondence, Nov 1954 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - OSA - Correspondence, Dec 1954 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - OSA - Correspondence, Jan 1955 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - OSA - Correspondence, Feb 1955 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - OSA - Correspondence, Mar 1955 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - OSA - Correspondence, Apr 1955 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - OSA - Correspondence, May 1955 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - OSA - Correspondence, Jun 1955 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - OSA - Correspondence, Jul 1955 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - OSA - Correspondence, Aug 1955 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - OSA - Master List of Phone Calls, Jul 1953-Jan 1954 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Politics, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Politics, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Politics, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Politics, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Politics, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Politics, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Politics, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Politics, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Politics, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Politics, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Politics - Campaign, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Politics - Local, 1961-1971 (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - Politics - Local, 1963-1975 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Politics - National, 1962-1978 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Random House - Consultancy on civil liberties book, 1969-1976 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Right-to-Sing Committee - defense of right to sing in Washington Square Park, New York City, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson - Vice Presidential Nomination, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Ross, Stanford G. - Commissioner of Social Security, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Scanlon's Monthly Contest - Norman Dorsen as judge for essay contest on freedom of the press, 1970-1971 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - School Bussing Letters, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Smith Act, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Social Security Universal Coverage Study, 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Society of American Law Teachers (SALT) - Affirmative Action, 1979-1985 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - SALT - Arkansas Case, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - SALT - Awards to Law Teachers, 1975-1979 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - SALT - Board and travel - Dean's list, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - SALT - Board of Governors, 1983-1985 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - SALT - Board of Governors, 1974-1982 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - SALT - Board of Governors, 1981-1983 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - SALT - Burger Court book, 1977-1982 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - SALT - By-laws, 1977-1980 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - SALT - Committee on Judicial Appointments, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - SALT - Committees, 1976-1980 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - SALT - Conference, Dec 1979 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - SALT - Conference on Legal Education, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - SALT - Defunis/Bakke, 1974-1977 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - SALT - Elections, 1979-1983 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - SALT - Exams, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - SALT - Foundation grants, operating expenses, miscellaneous monies, 1974-1979 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - SALT - Justice Douglas, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Includes one letter from U.S. Supreme Court Justice William O. Douglas.
  - SALT - Meeting, Dec 1975 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - SALT - Meeting, Apr 1976-Jun 1976 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - SALT - Meeting, Oct 1976 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - SALT - Meeting, Dec 1976 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - SALT - Meeting, Apr 1977 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - SALT - Meeting, Oct 1978 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - SALT - Meetings, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - SALT - Membership Correspondence, 1974-1977 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - SALT - Memberships, 1974-1982 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - SALT - Meskill, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - SALT - Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - SALT - Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - SALT - Miscellaneous, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - SALT - Miscellaneous, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - SALT - Miscellaneous, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - SALT - Miscellaneous, 1980-1981 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - SALT - Newsletter, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - SALT - Presentation pamphlet, Undated (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - SALT - Projects (general), 1975 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - SALT - Public statements, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - SALT - Statement on Second Circuit, 1974-1976 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - SALT - Statements, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - SALT - Statements, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - SALT - Teaching Conference - NYU Marden Program, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Society of Public Teachers of Law, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Stein Bill, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Stratton, Samuel, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Village Independent Democrats - Judgeship, 1964-1967 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Villers Foundation, 1981-1984 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - WQED Proposal for humanities television program (consultancy), 1973 (Box 27, Folder 31)
- Series V: Arthur Garfield Hays Civil Liberties Program
  - Annual report, 1963-1964 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Annual report, 1964-1965 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    Includes one letter from U.S. Senator Robert F. Kennedy and one letter from U.S. Supreme Court Justice Hugo L. Black.
  - Annual report, 1965-1966 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Annual report, 1966-1967 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Annual report, 1967-1968 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Annual report, 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Annual report, 1973-1976 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Annual report, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Annual report, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Annual report, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Article - Downs and Goldman paper, 1962-1963 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Conference - International Population Policy, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Conference - Poverty, Civil Liberties, and the Law, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Conference - Public Aid to Parochial Schools Conference, May 1962-Jun 1962 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Conference - Public Aid to Parochial Schools Conference, Mar 1962-Jun 1962 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Conference - Reed Rubin, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Conference - Role of the Supreme Court in Civil Liberties, 1963-1965 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Conference - Welfare, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Conference - Wiretapping, May 1961 (Box 28, Folder 13)